{
    "subject": "resource/University_of_the_East",
    "predicate": "property/nickname",
    "object": "resource/UE_Red_Warriors",
    "human_readable": "The nickname of University of the East is UE Red Warriors.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8246086239814758,
            "question": "What is the nickname of the University of the East?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7618110179901123,
            "question": "What are the University of the East known as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6676188111305237,
            "question": "What team name is associated with the University of the East?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6379970908164978,
            "question": "What nickname do fans use for the University of the East?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6117480993270874,
            "question": "What is the name used to refer to the University of the East's athletic program?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4972764551639557,
            "question": "Which term best describes the University of the East's sports identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4553997814655304,
            "question": "Which sports team represents the University of the East?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33553144335746765,
            "question": "What is a popular way to identify the University of the East in the athletic world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23605117201805115,
            "question": "How is the University of the East often addressed in sporting events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15070374310016632,
            "question": "What moniker reflects the spirit and pride of the University of the East?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The nickname of University of the East is UE Red Warriors.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6994_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the University of the East often addressed in sporting events?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6994_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is a popular way to identify the University of the East in the athletic world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6994_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which sports team represents the University of the East?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6994_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6994_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents support that the nickname of the University of the East (UE) varsity team, competing in the University Athletic Association of the Philippines, is the UE Red Warriors."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}